Guide to the Dayton Company Advertising Scrapbooks, 1904-1968
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Dayton Company Advertising Scrapbooks 1904-1968
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
Dayton Company (Target Corporation)
170 Linear Feet 509 Items
The Dayton Company, founded in 1902 in Minneapolis, Minn., was the predecessor firm to the Target Corporation, one of the largest retail chains in the United States.
The Dayton Company Advertising Scrapbooks collection spans the years 1904 through 1968 and consist of 509 bound scrapbooks of newspaper advertisements, fliers and circulars for the Dayton department store chain in Minneapolis and St. Paul, Minn. and Rochester, N.Y., as well for several of Dayton's competitors, affiliates and subsidiary department and discount stores, including B. Dalton Bookseller, the J.B. Hudson and L.S. Donaldson stores.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Dayton Company Advertising Scrapbooks were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2006.
Historical Note
1902 George D. Dayton bought Goodfellows store in Minneapolis, Minn., and assumed presidency of the company
1903 Goodfellows renamed as Dayton's Daylight Store; the company name changed to Dayton Dry Goods Company
1907 Dayton's took over Bargain Basement, where odd lots and discontinued merchandise was sold
1910 Dayton Dry Goods Company renamed as The Dayton Company
1916 Hugh Arthur hired as advertising manager
1917 Bargain Basement renamed the Downstairs Store
1918 Dayton Foundation created Delivery service began
1919 Air shipment and delivery began
1924 The Looking Glass and Sub-Deb specialty shops opened
1926 Men's store opened
1927 University store opened
1929 J.B. Hudson and Son acquired and renamed J.B. Hudson, Inc.
1935 Horse delivery service replaced by a truck fleet
1938 The Model Room, specializing in high fashion dresses, opened
1943 The Model Room renamed as The Oval Room
1947 New Sky Room opened
1948 Hugh Arthur retired as advertising director New Looking Glass specialty shop opened
1954 Dayton's Rochester store opened Fantle Bros. of Sioux Falls, S.D., acquired
1956 Southdale Center opened
1959 Schuneman's of St. Paul, Minn., acquired; eventually renamed Dayton's-St. Paul
1962 First Target discount store opened Brookdale Center opened
1965 B. Dalton Booksellers founded by the Dayton Co.
1967 Dayton Corporation first public stock offering Fantle Brothers reacquired by the Fantle family
1969 Dayton Corporation and J.L. Hudson Company merged to form the Dayton Hudson Corporation
1978 Mervyn's department stores acquired
1987 B. Dalton Booksellers sold to Barnes & Noble, Inc.
1990 Marshall Field's department stores acquired
2000 Dayton Hudson Corporation renamed as the Target Corporation
2004 Marshall's and Mervyn's chains are sold to allow Target to concentrate on discount merchandising
Collection Overview
The Dayton Company Advertising Scrapbooks collection spans the years 1904 through 1968 and consist of 509 bound scrapbooks of newspaper advertisements, fliers and circulars for the Dayton department store chain (the predecessor entity of the Target discount chain) in Minneapolis and St. Paul, Minn. and Rochester, N.Y., as well for several of Dayton's competitors, affiliates and subsidiary department and discount stores, including B. Dalton Bookseller, the J.B. Hudson and L.S. Donaldson stores.
The collection is organized into the categories of Affiliate and Subsidiary Stores advertising and Dayton Company advertising, therein alphabetically by store name, within which the volumes are arranged in roughly chronological order.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Dayton Corporation
Dayton Hudson Corporation
Dayton Company
Target Corporation -- History
L.S. Donaldson Company (Minneapolis, Minn.)
Donaldson's (Firm: Minneapolis, Minn.)
William Donaldson & Company (Minneapolis, Minn.)
J.B. Hudson & Son (Firm)
J.B. Hudson, Inc
B. Dalton Bookseller (Firm)
Department stores
Department stores -- Advertising
Department stores -- United States
Department stores -- United States -- History
Department stores -- United States -- History -- 20th century
Discount houses (Retail trade)
Discount houses (Retail trade) -- United States
Discount houses (Retail trade) -- United States -- History
Discount houses (Retail trade) -- United States -- History -- 20th century
Advertising, newspaper
Advertising fliers
Scrapbooks.
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Contents of Collection
- Affiliate and Subsidiary Stores Advertisements, 1914-1968, (24 boxes)
  - B. Dalton Bookseller, 1965-1968
    - 1965 Oct. 16-1968 Sept. 22 (Box 1)
  - Fantle Brothers, 1962-1964
    - 1962 Apr. 17-1963 Apr. 16 (Box 2)
    - 1963 Apr. 17-1964 May 15 (Box 3)
  - Home Furnishings, 1935-1937, 1944-1946
    - 1935 Oct. 1-1937 July 27 (Box 4)
    - 1944 Feb. 18-1946 July 23 (Box 5)
  - J.B. Hudson, 1929-1968
    - 1929 Oct. 30-1936 Mar. 12 (Box 6)
    - 1936 Mar. 18-1943 Oct. 28 (Box 7)
    - 1943 Nov. 2-1950 Feb. 9 (Box 8)
      Fragile condition: Some pages loose. Handle with care.
    - 1950 Feb. 10-Nov. 16 (Box 9)
    - 1953 Nov.-1955 Apr. 12 (Box 10)
    - 1955 Apr. 17-1963 Aug. 18 (Box 11)
      Fragile condition: Some pages loose. Some pages damaged. Damaged spine. Handle with care.
    - 1963 Oct. 27-1965 Apr. 25 (Box 12)
    - 1965 May 2-Dec. 26 (Box 13)
    - 1968 May 19-Sept. 29 (Box 14)
  - L.S. Donaldson's, 1947
    Donaldson's and Dayton were longtime rivals in Minneapolis; Donaldson's was eventually acquired by Dayton in 1995.
    - 1947 Jan.1-Mar. 6 (Box 15)
    - 1947 Mar. 7-May 3 (Box 16)
    - 1947 May 5-July 25 (Box 17)
  - Ride the Mails, 1956-1960
    - 1956 May 6-1959 Mar. 29 (Box 18)
    - 1959 Apr. 12-1960 May 1 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous (includes Donaldson's), 1944-1946
    - 1944 Aug. 13-1946 July 28 (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous (other), 1914-1915, 1926-1929
    - 1914 Feb. 15-1915 Mar. 6 (Box 21)
      Fragile condition: Damaged spine. Handle with care.
    - 1915 Feb. 18-May 10 (Box 22)
      Fragile condition: No cover or spine. Handle with care.
    - 1926 June 4-Sept. 13 (Box 23)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 24)
- Dayton Minneapolis, 1904-1968, (397 boxes)
  - Combined Downstairs store and non-Dayton, 1922-1924
    - 1922 Nov. 17-1924 Jan. 4 (Box 25)
  - Combined Upstairs stores, 1960-1961
    - 1960 Nov. 13-1961 Jan. 1 (Box 26)
  - Combined Upstairs, Downstairs stores, 1904-1955
    - 1904 July 20-1905 Dec. 29 (Box 27)
    - 1904 Nov. 1-1905 July 31 (Box 28)
      Fragile condition: Brittle paper. Water damage. Tar residue on cover. Handle with care.
    - 1906 Jan. 1-Dec. 28 (Box 29)
      Fragile condition: Damaged binding. Water damage. Handle with care.
    - 1907 Jan. 3-Nov. 7 (Box 30)
    - 1907 Nov. 11-1908 Sept. 11 (Box 31)
      Fragile condition: Brittle paper. Handle with care.
    - 1907 Nov. 11-1908 Sept. 11 (Box 32)
      Fragile condition: Water damage. Handle with care.
    - 1908 Sept. 15-1909 June 14 (Box 33)
      Fragile condition: Damaged binding. Mold stain. Handle with care.
    - 1909 June 16-Dec. 31 (Box 34)
    - 1910 Jan. 1-July 29 (Box 35)
    - 1910 Aug. 1-1911 Mar. 11 (Box 36)
    - 1912 May 1-Oct. 31 (Box 37)
    - 1912 June 21-1913 Feb. 5 (Box 38)
    - 1912 Nov. 1-1913 Apr. 23 (Box 39)
    - 1913 Sept. 15-Dec. 9 (Box 40)
    - 1913 Oct. 22-1914 Mar. 11 (Box 41)
    - 1914 Mar. 12-Sept. 3 (Box 42)
    - 1914 Sept. 1-1915 Feb. 8 (Box 43)
    - 1915 Feb. 9-July 23 (Box 44)
    - 1915 May 4-1916 June 19 (Box 45)
    - 1915 July 26-1916 Jan. 13 (Box 46)
      Fragile condition: Brittle paper. Damaged binding. Handle with care.
    - 1916 July 14-1917 Jan. 8 (Box 47)
    - 1916 Jan. 27-July 13 (Box 48)
    - 1917 Jan. 9-June 10 (Box 49)
    - 1917 June 11-Nov. 23 (Box 50)
    - 1917 Nov. 26-1918 Apr. 9 (Box 51)
    - 1918 Apr. 10-Sept. 10 (Box 52)
    - 1918 Sept. 11-Dec. 14 (Box 53)
    - 1918 Dec. 19-1919 Apr. 29 (Box 54)
    - 1919 Apr. 29-Sept. 30 (Box 55)
    - 1919 Oct. 1-1920 Feb. 11 (Box 56)
    - 1920 Feb. 13-June 30 (Box 57)
    - 1920 July 1-1921 Jan. 20 (Box 58)
    - 1921 Jan. 21-Sept. 15 (Box 59)
    - 1921 Sept. 16-1922 Apr. 29 (Box 60)
    - 1922 May 1-Dec. 15 (Box 61)
    - 1922 Dec. 18-1923 June 29 (Box 62)
    - 1923 June 30-1924 Jan. 1 (Box 63)
      Fragile condition: Some pages damaged. Handle with care.
    - 1924 Jan.1-June 9 (Box 64)
    - 1924 June 10-Dec. 8 (Box 65)
    - 1924 Dec. 9-1925 May 23 (Box 66)
    - 1925 Mar. 24-July 4 (Box 67)
    - 1925 May 25-Nov. 13 (Box 68)
    - 1925 Nov. 16-1926 Mar. 22 (Box 69)
    - 1926 Mar. 23-Aug. 27 (Box 70)
    - 1926 Aug. 30-1927 Jan. 4 (Box 71)
    - 1927 Jan. 5-May 17 (Box 72)
    - 1927 May 18-Oct. 17 (Box 73)
    - 1927 Oct. 18-1928 Mar. 10 (Box 74)
    - 1927 Nov. 10-1928 Feb. 7 (Box 75)
    - 1928 Mar. 12-Aug. 2 (Box 76)
    - 1928 Aug. 2-Dec. 21 (Box 77)
    - 1929 May 2-Oct. 7 (Box 78)
    - 1930 Jan. 27-Apr. 23 (Box 79)
    - 1930 July 22-Oct. 17 (Box 80)
    - 1930 Oct. 20-1931 Jan. 22 (Box 81)
    - 1931 Jan. 22-Apr. 3 (Box 82)
    - 1931 Apr. 6-June 26 (Box 83)
    - 1931 June 27-Sept. 22 (Box 84)
    - 1931 Sept. 23-Dec. 23 (Box 85)
    - 1931 Dec. 24-1932 Mar. 23 (Box 86)
    - 1932 Mar. 24-June 24 (Box 87)
    - 1932 June 25-Sept. 28 (Box 88)
    - 1932 Sept. 29-1933 Jan. 17 (Box 89)
    - 1933 Jan. 17-Apr. 19 (Box 90)
      Fragile condition: Damaged cover. Handle with care.
    - 1933 Apr. 20-July 19 (Box 91)
    - 1933 July 20-Oct. 26 (Box 92)
    - 1933 Oct. 27-1934 Jan. 27 (Box 93)
    - 1934 Jan. 29-May 7 (Box 94)
    - 1934 May 8-Aug. 24 (Box 95)
    - 1934 Aug. 27-Nov. 27 (Box 96)
    - 1934 Nov. 28-1935 Feb. 18 (Box 97)
    - 1935 Feb. 19-May 25 (Box 98)
    - 1935 May 27-Sept. 3 (Box 99)
    - 1935 Sept. 4-Dec. 12 (Box 100)
    - 1935 Dec. 13-1936 Mar. 18 (Box 101)
    - 1936 Mar. 19-June 26 (Box 102)
    - 1936 June 27-Oct. 15, 1937 July 8 (Box 103)
    - 1936 Oct. 6-1937 Jan. 4 (Box 104)
    - 1937 Jan. 5-Apr. 1 (Box 105)
    - 1937 Apr. 2-July 9 (Box 106)
    - 1937 July 12-Oct. 29 (Box 107)
    - 1937 Nov. 1-1938 Jan. 26 (Box 108)
    - 1938 Jan. 26-Apr. 20 (Box 109)
    - 1938 Apr. 21-July 13 (Box 110)
    - 1938 July 14-Oct. 25 (Box 111)
    - 1939 Jan. 20-Apr. 14 (Box 112)
    - 1939 Apr. 10-Sept. 12 (Box 113)
    - 1939 July 13-Oct. 31 (Box 114)
    - 1939 Sept. 13-1940 Feb. 2 (Box 115)
    - 1940 Feb. 5-June 25 (Box 116)
    - 1940 June 26-Dec. 6 (Box 117)
    - 1940 Dec. 9-1941 Apr. 18 (Box 118)
    - 1941 Apr. 21-Sept. 30 (Box 119)
    - 1941 Oct. 1-1942 Feb. 17 (Box 120)
    - 1942 Feb. 18-Aug. 28 (Box 121)
    - 1942 July 30-1943 Jan. 14 (Box 122)
    - 1943 Jan. 15-July 8 (Box 123)
    - 1943 July 9-Dec. 17 (Box 124)
    - 1943 Dec. 20-1944 May 16 (Box 125)
    - 1944 May 17-Nov. 18 (Box 126)
    - 1944 Nov. 20-1945 June 18 (Box 127)
      Fragile condition: Torn pages. Handle with care.
    - 1945 June 19-Dec. 12 (Box 128)
    - 1945 Dec. 13-1946 May 1 (Box 129)
    - 1946 May 2-Aug. 23 (Box 130)
    - 1946 Aug. 26-Dec. 18 (Box 131)
    - 1946 Dec. 19-1947 Mar. 12 (Box 132)
    - 1947 Mar. 13-May 15 (Box 133)
    - 1947 May 16-Sept. 9 (Box 134)
    - 1947 Aug. 4-Oct. 7 (Box 135)
    - 1947 Sept. 10-Dec. 8 (Box 136)
    - 1947 Oct. 8-Dec. 5 (Box 137)
    - 1947 Dec. 5-1948 Feb. 2 (Box 138)
    - 1947 Dec. 9-1948 Mar. 9 (Box 139)
    - 1948 Feb. 3-Mar. 27 (Box 140)
    - 1948 Mar. 10-June 16 (Box 141)
    - 1948 Mar. 29-May 26 (Box 142)
    - 1948 May 26-Aug. 18 (Box 143)
    - 1948 June 17-Sept. 30 (Box 144)
    - 1948 Aug. 19-Oct. 25 (Box 145)
    - 1948 Sept. 30-1949 Jan. 4 (Box 146)
    - 1948 Oct. 26-Dec. 27 (Box 147)
    - 1948 Dec. 2-1949 Mar. 10 (Box 148)
    - 1949 Mar. 11-May 19 (Box 149)
    - 1949 May 10-July 8 (Box 150)
    - 1949 July 9-Sept. 20 (Box 151)
    - 1949 Sept. 21-Nov. 23 (Box 152)
    - 1949 Oct. 16-Dec. 15 (Box 153)
    - 1949 Nov. 24-1950 Jan. 10 (Box 154)
    - 1949 Dec. 16-1950 Feb. 28 (Box 155)
    - 1950 Aug. 29-Oct. 11 (Box 156)
    - 1950 Oct. 12-Nov. 28 (Box 157)
    - 1950 Nov. 29-1951 Jan. 13 (Box 158)
    - 1951 Jan. 10-Mar. 31 (Box 159)
    - 1951 Mar. 13-May 7 (Box 160)
    - 1951 Apr. 5-June 1 (Box 161)
    - 1951 May 7-June 27 (Box 162)
    - 1951 June 28-Aug. 28 (Box 163)
    - 1951 Aug. 29-Oct. 17 (Box 164)
    - 1951 Oct. 18-Dec. 4 (Box 165)
    - 1951 Dec. 5-1952 Jan. 15 (Box 166)
    - 1952 Jan. 10-Mar. 11 (Box 167)
    - 1952 Feb. 18-Apr. 17 (Box 168)
    - 1952 Apr. 30-June 23 (Box 169)
    - 1952 June 24-Aug. 26 (Box 170)
    - 1952 June 24-Sept. 9 (Box 171)
    - 1952 Nov. 27-1953 Jan. 5 (Box 172)
    - 1953 Jan. 1-Mar. 7 (Box 173)
    - 1953 June 8-July 28 (Box 174)
    - 1953 July 29-Sept. 10 (Box 175)
    - 1953 Oct. 23-Dec. 1 (Box 176)
    - 1954 Dec. 14-1955 Feb. 13 (Box 177)
  - Dayton Dry Goods Store to The Dayton Company, 1911
    - 1911 Mar. 22-Nov. 13 (Box 178)
  - Downstairs store, 1911-1968
    - 1911 Feb. 22-July 21 (Box 179)
      Fragile condition: Mold stain. Handle with care.
    - 1920 July 1-1921 Sept. 17 (Box 180)
    - 1921 Sept.20-1922 Sept. 15 (Box 181)
    - 1922 Sept. 16-1923 Aug. 3 (Box 182)
    - 1923 Aug. 7-1924 May 9 (Box 183)
    - 1924 May 12-1925 Jan. 29 (Box 184)
    - 1925 Jan. 30-Sept. 25 (Box 185)
    - 1925 Oct. 7-1926 May 17 (Box 186)
    - 1926 May 11-Dec. 3 (Box 187)
    - 1926 Dec. 6-1927 July 13 (Box 188)
      Fragile condition: Damaged binding. Handle with care.
    - 1927 July 14-1928 Mar. 1 (Box 189)
    - 1928 Mar. 2-Sept. 27 (Box 190)
    - 1928 Sept. 28-1929 Apr. 10 (Box 191)
    - 1929 Oct. 28-1930 June 18 (Box 192)
    - 1936 May 11-1937 Jan. 22 (Box 193)
    - 1937 Jan. 25-Sept. 30 (Box 194)
    - 1937 Oct. 1-1938 June 1 (Box 195)
    - 1938 June 2-1939 Feb. 6 (Box 196)
    - 1939 Feb. 7-Oct. 25 (Box 197)
    - 1939 Oct. 26-1940 June 21 (Box 198)
    - 1940 June 26-1941 Apr. 18 (Box 199)
    - 1941 Apr. 21-1942 Jan. 30 (Box 200)
    - 1942 Jan. 31-Oct. 22 (Box 201)
    - 1942 Oct. 23-1943 Sept. 9 (Box 202)
    - 1944 July 16-1945 May 5 (Box 203)
    - 1945 Mar. 2-1946 Jan. 18 (Box 204)
    - 1946 Jan. 18-Sept. 4 (Box 205)
    - 1947 Apr. 17-Nov. 17 (Box 206)
    - 1947 Nov. 18-1948 May 19 (Box 207)
    - 1949 Mar. 8-Nov. 30 (Box 208)
    - 1949 Dec. 1-1950 July 28 (Box 209)
    - 1950 July 31-1951 Mar. 22 (Box 210)
    - 1951 Mar. 23-Nov. 6 (Box 211)
    - 1951 Nov. 7-1952 June 17 (Box 212)
    - 1952 June 18-1953 Feb. 2 (Box 213)
    - 1953 Feb. 3-Aug. 31 (Box 214)
    - 1953 Sept. 1-1954 Mar. 4 (Box 215)
    - 1954 Mar. 5-Aug. 26 (Box 216)
    - 1954 Aug. 27-1955 Apr. 1 (Box 217)
    - 1955 Apr. 1-Oct. 14 (Box 218)
    - 1955 Oct. 16-1956 May 13 (Box 219)
    - 1956 May 13-Dec. 12 (Box 220)
    - 1956 Dec. 13-1957 Aug. 27 (Box 220A)
    - 1957 Aug. 28-1958 Apr. 16 (Box 221)
    - 1958 Apr. 17-Nov. 5 (Box 222)
    - 1958 Nov. 6-1959 May 3 (Box 223)
    - 1959 May 4-Nov. 8 (Box 224)
    - 1959 Nov. 8-1960 May 3 (Box 225)
    - 1960 May 4-Nov. 25 (Box 226)
    - 1960 Nov. 27-1961 June 22 (Box 227)
    - 1961 June 23-1962 Feb. 5 (Box 228)
    - 1962 Feb. 6-1963 Jan. 13 (Box 229)
    - 1963 Jan. 14-Sept. 3 (Box 230)
    - 1963 Sept. F2255-1964 Apr. 13 (Box 231)
    - 1964 Apr. 12-Dec. 8 (Box 232)
    - 1964 Dec. 9-1965 July 22 (Box 233)
    - 1965 July 23-1966 Mar. 13 (Box 234)
    - 1966 Apr. 13-Sept. 16 (Box 235)
    - 1966 Sept. 18-1967 Apr. 18 (Box 236)
    - 1967 Apr. 17-Nov. 19 (Box 237)
    - 1967 Nov. 23-1968 Aug. 15 (Box 238)
    - 1968 Aug. 18-Oct. 7 (Box 239)
  - Hugh Arthur copies, 1924-1947
    Arthur was Dayton's advertising manager from 1916 unti his retirement in 1948.
    - 1924 Nov. 19-1925 Mar. 23 (Box 240)
    - 1925 July 6-Oct. 22 (Box 241)
    - 1925 Oct. 23-1926 Jan. 25 (Box 242)
    - 1926 Jan. 26-Apr. 26 (Box 243)
    - 1926 Apr. 21-Aug. 2 (Box 244)
    - 1926 Aug. 3-Nov. 1 (Box 245)
    - 1926 Nov. 2-1927 Jan. 27 (Box 246)
    - 1927 Jan. 28-May 2 (Box 247)
    - 1927 May 3-Aug. 10 (Box 248)
    - 1927 Aug. 11-Nov. 9 (Box 249)
    - 1928 Feb. 7-May 12 (Box 250)
    - 1928 May 14-Aug. 10 (Box 251)
    - 1928 Aug. 13-Nov. 9 (Box 252)
    - 1928 Nov. 12-1929 Jan. 30 (Box 253)
    - 1929 Jan. 31-Apr. 27 (Box 254)
    - 1929 Apr. 29-July 29 (Box 255)
    - 1929 July 30-Oct. 29 (Box 256)
    - 1929 Oct. 30-1930 Jan. 25 (Box 257)
    - 1930 Apr. 24-July 21 (Box 258)
    - 1938 Oct. 26-1939 Jan. 19 (Box 259)
    - 1939 Apr. 15-July 12 (Box 260)
    - 1939 Nov. 1-1940 Jan. 22 (Box 261)
    - 1940 Jan. 23-Apr. 19 (Box 262)
    - 1940 Apr. 22-July 23 (Box 263)
    - 1940 July 24-Nov. 15 (Box 264)
    - 1940 Nov. 18-1941 Feb. 11 (Box 265)
    - 1941 Feb. 11-May 26 (Box 266)
    - 1941 May 27-Sept. 3 (Box 267)
    - 1941 Sept. 4-Dec. 16 (Box 268)
    - 1941 Dec. 17-1942 Mar. 25 (Box 269)
    - 1942 Mar. 26-July 1 (Box 270)
    - 1942 July 1-Oct. 14 (Box 271)
    - 1942 Oct. 14-1943 Feb. 1 (Box 272)
    - 1943 Feb. 1-May 20 (Box 273)
    - 1943 May 21-Sept. 24 (Box 274)
    - 1943 Sept. 27-Dec. 30 (Box 275)
    - 1944 Jan. 1-Mar. 29 (Box 276)
    - 1944 Mar. 30-July 21 (Box 277)
    - 1944 July 24-Nov. 14 (Box 278)
    - 1944 Nov. 15-1945 Mar. 19 (Box 279)
    - 1945 Mar. 20-July 18 (Box 280)
    - 1945 July 19-Nov. 6 (Box 281)
    - 1945 Nov. 6-1946 Feb. 21 (Box 282)
    - 1946 Feb. 21-May 7 (Box 283)
    - 1946 May 8-July 16 (Box 284)
    - 1946 July 17-Oct. 2 (Box 285)
    - 1946 Oct. 1-Nov. 14 (Box 286)
    - 1946 Nov. 15-Dec. 30 (Box 287)
    - 1947 Jan. 1-Feb. 14 (Box 288)
    - 1947 Feb. 15-Mar. 31 (Box 289)
    - 1947 Apr. 1-May 10 (Box 290)
    - 1947 May 10-Aug. 2 (Box 291)
  - Newspaper: Daily Herald, 1962
    - 1962 May 16-Aug. 13 (Box 292)
  - Newspaper: Star and Tribune, 1955-1959
    - 1955 Jan. 24-Apr. 15 (Box 293)
    - 1955 Apr. 5-May 21 (Box 294)
    - 1955 Apr. 16-June 13 (Box 295)
    - 1955 May 22-July 8 (Box 296)
    - 1955 June 14-Aug. 22 (Box 297)
    - 1955 July 10-Aug. 28 (Box 298)
    - 1955 Aug. 23-Oct. 14 (Box 299)
    - 1955 Aug. 28-Oct. 7 (Box 300)
    - 1955 Oct. 16-Nov. 30 (Box 301)
    - 1955 Oct. 9-Nov. 14 (Box 302)
    - 1955 Nov. 30-1956 Jan. 26 (Box 303)
    - 1956 Jan. 27-Apr. 1 (Box 304)
    - 1956 Apr. 1-May 28 (Box 305)
    - 1956 May 30-Aug. 19 (Box 306)
    - 1959 Oct. 26-Dec. 7 (Box 307)
  - Upstairs store, 1938, 1950-1968
    - 1938 Feb. 7-June 23 (Box 308)
    - 1938 June 24-Nov. 18 (Box 309)
    - 1938 Nov. 21-1939 Apr. 7 (Box 310)
    - 1950 Jan. 11-Mar. 4 (Box 311)
    - 1950 Mar. 1-May 17 (Box 312)
    - 1950 Mar. 1-May 5 (Box 313)
    - 1950 May 18-Aug. 7 (Box 314)
    - 1950 May 8-June 26 (Box 315)
    - 1950 June 27-Aug. 28 (Box 316)
    - 1950 Aug. 8-Oct. 3 (Box 317)
    - 1950 Aug. 8-Oct. 11 (Box 318)
    - 1950 Oct. 4-Nov. 28 (Box 319)
    - 1950 Nov. 29-1951 Jan. 23 (Box 320)
    - 1951 Jan. 24-Apr. 4 (Box 321)
    - 1951 June 2-Aug. 15 (Box 322)
    - 1951 Aug. 16-Oct. 13 (Box 323)
    - 1951 Oct. 15-Dec. 10 (Box 324)
    - 1951 Dec. 11-1952 Feb. 16 (Box 325)
    - 1952 Mar. 12-Apr. 29 (Box 326)
    - 1952 Apr. 18-June 23 (Box 327)
    - 1952 Aug. 27-Oct. 10 (Box 328)
    - 1952 Sept. 10-Nov. 7 (Box 329)
    - 1952 Oct. 11-Nov. 25 (Box 330)
    - 1952 Nov. 10-Dec. 31 (Box 331)
    - 1953 Jan. 1-Mar. 19 (Box 332)
    - 1953 Mar. 19-May 15 (Box 333)
    - 1953 Apr. 23-June 6 (Box 334)
    - 1953 May 16-July 20 (Box 335)
    - 1953 July 21-Sept. 15 (Box 336)
    - 1953 Sept. 1-Oct. 22 (Box 337)
    - 1953 Sept. 16-Nov. 6 (Box 338)
    - 1953 Nov. 7-Dec. 28 (Box 339)
    - 1953 Dec. 28-1954 Feb. 28 (Box 340)
    - 1954 Mar. 1-Apr. 23 (Box 341)
    - 1954 Apr. 25-July 1 (Box 342)
    - 1954 Sept. 17-Nov. 15 (Box 343)
    - 1954 Nov. 15-1955 Jan. 24 (Box 344)
    - 1955 Feb. 14-Apr. 4 (Box 345)
    - 1956 Aug. 20-Oct. 22 (Box 346)
    - 1956 Oct. 22-Dec. 10 (Box 347)
    - 1956 Dec. 11-1957 Feb. 27 (Box 348)
    - 1957 Feb. 28-May 7 (Box 349)
    - 1957 May 8-July 19 (Box 350)
    - 1957 July 22-Sept. 9 (Box 351)
    - 1957 Sept. 10-Nov. 9 (Box 352)
    - 1957 Nov. 10-Dec. 25 (Box 353)
    - 1957 Dec. 26-1958 Mar. 18 (Box 354)
    - 1958 Mar. 19-May 15 (Box 355)
    - 1958 May 16-July 22 (Box 356)
    - 1958 July 23-Sept. 19 (Box 357)
    - 1958 Sept. 20-Nov. 18 (Box 358)
    - 1958 Nov. 14-Dec. 22 (Box 359)
    - 1958 Dec. 23-1959 Mar. 10 (Box 360)
    - 1959 Mar. 11-May 8 (Box 361)
    - 1959 May 10-July 16 (Box 362)
    - 1959 July 17-Sept. 7 (Box 363)
    - 1959 Sept. 8-Oct. 26 (Box 364)
    - 1959 Dec. 7-1960 Feb. 4 (Box 365)
    - 1960 Feb. 5-Apr. 3 (Box 366)
    - 1960 Apr. 3-May 20 (Box 367)
    - 1960 May 22-July 29 (Box 368)
    - 1960 July 31-Sept. 16 (Box 369)
    - 1960 Sept. 18-Nov. 11 (Box 370)
    - 1961 Jan. 2-Mar. 6 (Box 371)
    - 1961 Mar. 7-May 5 (Box 372)
    - 1961 May 7-July 18 (Box 373)
    - 1961 July 19-Sept. 22 (Box 374)
    - 1961 Sept. 22-Nov. 26 (Box 375)
    - 1961 Nov. 26-1962 Jan. 28 (Box 376)
    - 1962 Jan. 29-Apr. 6 (Box 377)
    - 1962 Apr. 8-Sept. 26 (Box 378)
    - 1962 Sept. 27-Nov. 23 (Box 379)
    - 1962 Nov. 25-1963 Feb. 13 (Box 380)
    - 1963 Feb. 14-Apr. 22 (Box 381)
    - 1963 Apr. 23-June 25 (Box 382)
    - 1963 June 25-Aug. 15 (Box 383)
    - [Box number omitted during processing; listed here as a dummy container for continuity purposes.] (Box [384])
    - 1963 Sept. 16-Nov. 20 (Box 385)
    - 1963 Nov. 20-1964 Jan. 15 (Box 386)
    - 1964 Jan. 16-Mar. 18 (Box 387)
    - 1964 Mar. 18-May 10 (Box 388)
    - 1964 May 10-July 10 (Box 389)
    - 1964 July 12-Sept. 16 (Box 390)
    - 1964 Sept. 17-Nov. 8 (Box 391)
    - 1964 Nov. 8-1965 Jan. 3 (Box 392)
    - 1965 Jan. 4-Mar. 12 (Box 393)
    - 1965 Mar. 12-May 3 (Box 394)
    - 1965 May 2-June 29 (Box 395)
    - 1965 June 29-Sept. 8 (Box 396)
    - 1965 Sept. 8-Oct. 21 (Box 397)
    - 1965 Oct. 20-Dec. 5 (Box 398)
    - 1965 Dec. 5-1966 Feb. 9 (Box 399)
    - 1966 Feb. 10-Apr. 3 (Box 400)
    - 1966 Apr. 3-May 13 (Box 401)
    - 1966 May 13-July 13 (Box 402)
    - 1966 July 14-Aug. 29 (Box 403)
    - 1966 Aug. 29-Oct. 18 (Box 404)
    - 1966 Oct. 19-Nov. 20 (Box 405)
    - 1966 Nov. 30-1967 Jan. 9 (Box 406)
    - 1967 Jan. 9-Apr. 17 (Box 407)
    - 1967 Mar. 8-Apr. 17 (Box 408)
    - 1967 Apr. 17-May 21 (Box 409)
    - 1967 May 21-July 5 (Box 410)
    - 1967 July 5-Aug. 30 (Box 411)
    - 1967 Aug. 30-Oct. 8 (Box 412)
    - 1967 Oct. 8-Nov. 15 (Box 413)
    - 1967 Nov. 15-Dec. 14 (Box 413A)
    - 1967 Dec. 15-1968 Feb. 8 (Box 414)
    - 1968 Feb. 8-Apr. 1 (Box 415)
    - 1968 Apr. 1-May 6 (Box 416)
    - 1968 May 7-June 13 (Box 417)
    - 1968 July 13-Aug. 18 (Box 418)
    - 1968 Aug. 18-Aug. 29 (Box 419)
    - 1968 Aug. 18-Oct. 22 (Box 420)
    - 1968 Oct. 22-Nov. 6 (Box 421)
- Dayton Rochester, 1954-1968, (42 boxes)
  - Downstairs store, 1954-1968
    - 1954 Mar. 8-Dec. 2 (Box 422)
    - 1954 Dec. 3-1955 June 13 (Box 423)
    - 1956 July 30-1957 Jan. 30 (Box 424)
    - 1958 Apr. 30-1961 Feb. 10 (Box 425)
    - 1961 Feb. 13-1964 Feb. 12 (Box 426)
    - 1964 Feb. 17-1967 Apr. 17 (Box 427)
    - 1967 Apr. 19-1968 Oct. 22 (Box 428)
  - Upstairs store, 1954-1968
    - 1954 Jan. 4-Oct. 25 (Box 429)
    - 1954 Oct. 26-1955 May 24 (Box 430)
    - 1955 May 25-Oct. 25 (Box 431)
    - 1955 Oct. 25-1956 June 7 (Box 432)
    - 1956 June 7-Dec. 25 (Box 433)
    - 1956 Dec. 26-1957 May 22 (Box 434)
    - 1957 May 23-Oct. 11 (Box 435)